Guide to the E. B. White collection, 1899-1985.
White, E. B. collection, 1899-1985
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
E. B. White collection, 1899-1985.
4619
E. B. (Elwyn Brooks) White, 1899-
96.9 linear ft.
Manuscripts, letters, documents, clippings, photographs, filmstrips, film reels, notecards, cassette tapes, bound photocopies, medals, and awards.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Manuscripts, letters, documents, clippings, photographs, filmstrips, film reels, notecards, cassette tapes, bound photocopies, medals and awards by, to, or about E.B. White, spanning the entire range of his activities throughout his life.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
American essayist and author.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Manuscripts, letters, documents, clippings, photographs, filmstrips, film reels, notecards, cassette tapes, bound photocopies, medals and awards by, to, or about E.B. White, spanning the entire range of his activities throughout his life. Letters consist of ca. 3,000 letters by White and 25,000 letters to him from others; manuscripts include drafts, notes, and some galley proofs for his books Charlotte's Web, The Elements of Style, the Essays of E.B. White, the Letters of E.B. White, One Man's Meat, The Points of My Compass, Poems and Sketches, and Stuart Little, as well as drafts of his "Notes and comment" and "Talk of the Town" columns for the New Yorker magazine from 1934-1953. Printed items include White's contributions to the New Yorker and other magazines, his editorials for his high school newspaper, and ca. 350 articles about him, including interviews and reviews. Photographs include a large portrait photo of White, ca. 1950, and a family group photo taken at the 50th wedding anniversary of Samuel T. White and Jesse White in 1929, with E.B. and Katherine Sergeant White included in the group. Films include Maine Lobsterman, narrated by White and produced for the television show Omnibus in 1954, and The Family That Dwelt Apart, written and also narrated by White. Also included in the collection are objects such as E.B. White's typewriter, desk, and table.
Correspondents include: Katharine Sergeant White (his wife), James Thurber, Frank Sullivan, Harold Ross, William Shawn, Gus Lobrano, S.J. Perelman, Nathaniel Benchley, Howard Cushman, Alice Burchfield Sumner, Scott Elledge, and publishers such as Harper & Row, Farrar, Straus, and Giroux, and Macmillan.
SUBJECTS
Names:
White, E. B. (Elwyn Brooks), 1899-; Benchley, Nathaniel, 1915-; Cushman, Howard.; Elledge, Scott.; Lobrano, Gustav Stubbs.; Perelman, S. J. (Sidney Joseph), 1904-; Ross, Harold Wallace, 1892-1951.; Shawn, William.; Sullivan, Frank, 1892-; Sumner, Alice Burchfield.; Thurber, James, 1894-1961.; White, Katharine Sergeant Angell.; Farrar, Straus and Giroux, Inc.; Harper & Row, Publishers.; Macmillan & Co.
Titles:
New Yorker.
Subjects:
American literature--20th century.; Journalism--United States.; American literature--History and criticism.; American fiction--20th century--Sources.; American wit and humor.; Authors, American.; Humorists, American.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Portraits.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Book collection also held at the repository, including virtually all editions of White's books. Related manuscript and book collections also held at the repository concerning New Yorker writers A.J. Liebling, Frank Sullivan, and James Thurber.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Organized into the following major series: Manuscripts by White; miscellaneous printed material; letters received by White; letters written by him; fan letters received by him; and other materials.
Manuscripts arranged alphabetically by book title; letters received by White, alphabetically by correspondent; letters written by White, in chronological order; fan letters received, alphabetically by subject.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
Box 1-58; 263
Series II. Correspondence
Boxes 59-219; 260-261; 266
Outgoing Correspondence
Incoming Correspondence
Miscellaneous and Solicitations
Readers Mail from Harper's
Incoming Correspondence from Readers
Series III. Photographs, Printed Material, and Whiteiana
Boxes 220A-230; 260; 266
Photographs
Printed Material
Whiteiana
Series IV. Medals, Awards and Clippings
Boxes 231-240; 258; 260; Mapcase Folder 3 and 4
Medals and Awards
Clippings
Series V. Harper and Row Files
Boxes 241-243
Series VI. Macmillan Publishing Company files related to Elements of Style
Box 267
Series VII. Books on E.B. White by Others
Boxes 244-257; 259; Mapcase Folder 2
Scott Elledge, E.B. White: A Biography
Katherine Romans Hall, E.B. White: A Bibliographic Catalogue
Series VII. Miscellaneous (mainly oversize)
Boxes 260 and 262; Museum Items
Series VIII. Adaptations, Films, and Recordings
Boxes 260; 264-266; Mapcase Folder 1
Adaptations and Recordings of Charlotte's Web
Adaptations and Recordings of Stuart Little
Films and Recordings (not based on books)
CONTAINER LIST
- Manuscripts
  - A-Cg (Box 1)
  - Charlotte's Web (Box 2-3)
  - Che-K (Box 4)
  - Elements of Style 1 1st and 2nd edition (Box 5)
  - Elements of Style 2 2nd edition (Box 6)
  - Essays of E. B. White galley proofs (Box 263)
  - Letters of E.B. White
    - 1 (Box 7)
    - 2 (Box 8)
    - 3 (Box 9)
  - L-Le (Box 10)
  - Letters typescript
    - I-VI (Box 11)
    - VII-X (Box 12)
    - XI- (Box 13)
  - Letters Letters omitted
    - I-X (Box 14)
    - XI-XX (Box 15)
    - XXI-XXIX (Box 16)
    - XXX-XXXIX (Box 17)
    - XL-XLIX (Box 18)
    - L-LIX (Box 19)
  - Letters footnotes
    - I-VIII (Box 20)
    - IX-XVI (Box 21)
    - XVII-XXIII (Box 22)
    - XXIX-XXXI (Box 23)
    - XXXII-XXXVII (Box 24)
    - XXXVIII-XLIX (Box 25)
  - Letters queries
    - I-V (Box 26)
    - VI-X (Box 27)
  - Letters gallery
    - A (Box 28)
    - B (1) (Box 29)
    - B (2) (Box 30)
    - C (Box 31)
    - D (Box 32)
    - E (Box 33)
    - E + F (Box 34)
    - F + G (Box 35)
    - F + Misc. (Box 36)
    - Page proofs (Box 37)
  - Lf-Note (Box 38)
  - "Notes and Comments"
    - July 7, 1934-June 29, 1935 (Box 39)
    - July 6, 1935-June 27, 1936 (Box 40)
    - July 4, 1936-Nov. 4, 1939 (Box 41)
    - Feb. 3, 1940-Dec. 30, 1944 (Box 42)
    - 1945-1947 (Box 43)
    - 1948-1950 (Box 44)
    - Jan. 6, 1951-June 20, 1953 (Box 45)
    - July 18, 1953- (Box 46)
  - O-One Man's Meat (Box 47)
  - One Man's Meat-Onward and Upward in (Box 48)
  - "Onward and Upward with the Arts"-Poem (Box 49)
  - Poems and Sketches
    - 1 (Box 50)
    - 2 (Box 51)
    - 3 (Box 52)
    - 4 (Box 53)
  - Poems-Points (Box 54)
  - Points of My Compass - final draft and postscript (Box 55)
  - Poj-Stt (Box 56)
  - Stu-Th (Box 57)
  - Ti-Z (Box 58)
- Correspondence
  - Outgoing Correspondence
    - n.d.-1910 (Box 59)
    - 1911-1935 (Box 60)
    - 1936-1941 (Box 61)
    - 1942-1947 (Box 62)
    - 1948 (Box 63)
    - 1949-Feb. 1950 (Box 64)
    - Mar. 1950-1951 (Box 65)
    - 1952-Apr. 1953 (Box 66)
    - May 1953-1954 (Box 67)
    - 1955-1958 (Box 68)
    - 1959-1963 (Box 69)
    - 1964-1969 (Box 70)
    - 1970-1973 (Box 71)
    - 1974-Apr. 1976 (Box 72)
    - May 1976-Mar. 1977 (Box 73)
    - Apr. 1977-Oct. 1977 (Box 74)
    - Nov. 1977-Apr. 1978 (Box 75)
    - May 1978-Dec. 1978 (Box 76)
    - 1979 (Box 77)
    - 1980 (Box 78)
    - 1981 (Box 79)
    - 1982 (Box 80)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 81)
    - E.B.W. to S. Elledge (Box 82)
    - New Yorker Book A-I (Box 83)
    - New Yorker Book J-Rosr (Box 84)
    - New Yorker Book Ross, Harold Wallace (Box 85)
    - New Yorker Book Rost-Z (Box 86)
    - Albert, Mildred, and William White, 1943-1981 (Box 261)
    - Copies of Correspondence, c. 1934-1970 (Box 260, Folder 2-3)
      Note on envelopes read "Some included in the book, some not"
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - A-Alk (Box 87)
    - All-Allen, Q (Box 88)
    - Allen, R-Anf (Box 89)
    - Ang-Angell, Q (Box 90)
    - Angell, Roger-Atk (Box 91)
    - Atl-Bd (Box 92)
    - Be-Bez (Box 93)
    - Bf-Bl (Box 94)
    - Bm-Brc (Box 95)
    - Brd-Brittingham, L (Box 96)
    - Brittingham, M-Brown, Q (Box 97)
    - Brown, R-Bz (Box 98)
    - C-Cd (Box 99)
    - Ce-Cld (Box 100)
    - Cle-Con (Box 101)
    - Coo-Corn (Box 102)
    - Cornell Dept. of Rare Books A-H (Box 103)
    - Cornell Dept. of Rare Books I-Z (Box 104)
    - Coro-Ct (Box 105)
    - Cu-Cushman, H (1959) (Box 106)
    - Cushman, H (1960)-Cz (Box 107)
    - Da (Box 108)
    - Db-Dh (Box 109)
    - Di-Dz (Box 110)
    - E-Em (Box 111)
    - En-Ez (Box 112)
    - F-Fh (Box 113)
    - Fi-Fl (Box 114)
    - Fm-Fz (Box 115)
    - G-Gn (Box 116)
    - Go-Grd (Box 117)
    - Gre-Gs (Box 118)
    - Gt-Gus (Box 119)
    - Gut-Gz (Box 120)
    - H-Haro (Box 121)
    - Harper-Harper, firm (1947) (Box 122)
    - Harper, firm 1947-1959 (Box 123)
    - Harper, firm 1960- (Box 124)
    - Harper's-Hd (Box 125)
    - He (Box 126)
    - Hf-Hn (Box 127)
    - Hoa-Hot (Box 128)
    - Hou-Hz (Box 129)
    - I-Illian, K (Box 130)
    - Illian, L-Iz (Box 131)
    - J (Box 132)
    - Ka-Ke (Box 133)
    - Kf-Kz (Box 134)
    - L-Lea (Box 135)
    - Leb-Loa (Box 136)
    - Lob-Loq (Box 137)
    - Lor-Lz (Box 138)
    - M-Macl (Box 139)
    - Macm (Box 140)
    - Macn-Marb (Box 141)
    - Marc-Md (Box 142)
    - Me-Moo (Box 143)
    - Mop-Mz (Box 144)
    - N-New Yorker (1947) (Box 145)
    - New Yorker 1948-1981 (Box 146)
    - New Yorker (various) (Box 147)
    - New Yorker A-O (Box 148)
    - Pa-Pd (Box 149)
    - Pe (Box 150)
    - Pf-Pp (Box 151)
    - Po-Q (Box 152)
    - R-Rh (Box 153)
    - Ri-Rn (Box 154)
    - Ro-Rosr (Box 155)
    - Ross-Rz (Box 156)
    - S-Sd (Box 157)
    - Se-Sh (Box 158)
    - Si-Smith, Edm (Box 159)
    - Smith, Edn-Staa (Box 160)
    - Stab (Box 161)
    - Stac-Ste (Box 162)
    - Stix and Gude (Box 163)
    - Stf-Stt (Box 164)
    - Stu-Sz (Box 165)
    - Sumner, Alice Birchfield (outgoing) (Box 166)
    - T-Tg (Box 167)
    - Temple, Martha White (Box 168)
    - Tha-Thurber, H (Box 169)
    - Thurber, J-Thz (Box 170)
    - Ti-Tz (Box 171)
    - U-V (Box 172)
    - W-Wa (Box 173)
    - Wb-Whh (Box 174)
    - White, Allene (Box 175)
    - Whi-White, E. (Box 176)
    - White, F-White, Jessie (Box 177)
    - Joel White manuscripts and correspondence 1936-1950 (Box 178)
    - Joel White manuscripts and correspondence 1950- (Box 179)
  - White, Katharine Sergeant
    - undated-1933 (outgoing) (Box 180)
    - 1934-1949 (outgoing) (Box 181)
    - 1950-1977 (outgoing) (Box 182)
    - A-Scott Elledge (Box 183)
    - L-Ss (Box 184)
    - White, Stanley Hart (Box 185)
    - Stb-Wie (Box 186)
    - Wif-Will (Box 187)
    - Williamson-Wim (Box 188)
    - Wiri-Wri (Box 189)
    - Wrj-Z (Box 190)
  - Miscellaneous and Solicitations
    - undated-1977 (Box 191)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 192)
    - 1979-1984 (Box 193)
  - Reader's mail from Harper's
    - 1 (Box 194)
    - 2 (Box 195)
    - 3 (Box 196)
    - 4 (Box 197)
  - Incoming Correspondence from Readers
    - A-C (Box 198)
    - Charlotte's Web (Box 199-201)
    - Charlotte's Web-Elements (Box 202)
    - Elements-General (Box 203)
    - General (Box 204-209)
    - General-K (Box 210)
    - Letters of E.B. White (Box 211-212)
    - Le-One (Box 213)
    - Onf-Stt (Box 214)
    - Stuart Little (Box 215)
    - Stuart Little-Sympathy (Box 216)
    - Sympathy-Z (Box 217)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 218)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 219)
- Photographs, Printed Materials and Whiteiania
  - Photographs
    - EBW alone or with others (Box 220A)
    - Others (Box 220B)
    - S.T. White's stereoptican collection (Box 221)
    - Photographs of Cass Caufield and Bill Maxwell from the National Book Committee, 1972 (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - Photograph of Honorary Award recipients at Harvard (includes E.B. White), Undated (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - Photograph of E.B. White and the White Family (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - Printed Material
    - 1910-1929 (Box 222)
    - 1930-1939 (Box 223)
    - 1940-1949 (Box 224)
    - 1960-1969 (Box 226)
    - 1970-1975 (Box 227)
    - 1976- (Box 228)
    - (Box 229)
  - Whiteiana (Box 230)
- Medals, Awards, and Clippings
  - Medals and Awards
    - I (Box 231)
    - II (Box 232)
    - The Newspaper Guild of New York Page One Literature Award for "The Second Tree from the Corner", 1954 (Box 260, Folder 8)
    - Honorary Degrees (Folder 3)
  - Clippings
    - (Box 233)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 234)
    - (sorted) (Box 235)
    - Box II (Box 236)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 237)
    - About E.B. White 1 (Box 238)
    - About E.B. White 2 (Box 239)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 240)
    - Printed scrapbook (Box 258)
      Loose photocopies of clippings and articles
    - NY Times clipping listing Pulitzer Prize winners, including E.B. White, 1978-04-18 (Folder 4)
- Harper & Row files
  - Trade I (Property of Harper & Row) (Box 241)
  - Trade II (Property of Harper & Row) (Box 242)
  - Various (Property of Harper & Row) (Box 243)
- Macmillan Publishing Company files related to Elements of Style
  This series contains files originally held by MacMillan Publishing company and includes correspondence, manuscripts, drafts, reviews, and clippings related to the publications of the first three editions of The Elements of Style.
  - Correspondence 1976-1977, 1976-1977 (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence 1978, 1978 (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 1979, 1979 (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence 1980-1981, 1980-1981 (Box 267, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence 1982-1983, 1982-1983 (Box 267, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence 1984, 1984 (Box 267, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence 1985-1987, 1985-1987 (Box 267, Folder 7)
  - Elements of Style 3rd edition - revision, 1978 (Box 276, Folder 8)
  - Elements of Style 3rd edition - revision, 1978 (Box 276, Folder 9)
    D.A.E. suggestions
  - Elements of Style 3rd edition - revision, 1978 (Box 276, Folder 10-11)
  - Elements of Style 3rd edition - tearsheets, 1978 (Box 276, Folder 12)
  - Elements of Style 2nd edition - revised preface, 1972 (Box 276, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence related to 2nd edition, 1968-1975 (Box 267, Folder 14)
  - Elements of Style 1st edition, 1957-1959 (Box 276, Folder 15-17)
  - Elements of Style 1st edition - notes and feedback, 1957-1959 (Box 276, Folder 18)
  - Elements of Style 1st edition - discarded material, 1957-1959 (Box 276, Folder 19)
  - Elements of Style 1st edition - uncorrected proof, 1959 (Box 276, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence related to 1st edition, 1958-1979 (Box 267, Folder 21)
    Also includes correspondence related to later editions.
  - News clippings, 1959 (Box 267, Folder 22)
  - News clippings and reviews, 1959-1978 (Box 267, Folder 23)
  - News clippings, correspondence, and reviews, 1960-1978 (Box 267, Folder 24)
  - 2nd edition reviews, 1972-1979 (Box 267, Folder 25-26)
  - 2nd edition marketing, 1967-1974 (Box 267, Folder 27)
  - 3rd edition press materials, 1975-1993 (Box 267, Folder 28)
  - 3rd edition press releases, 1979 (Box 267, Folder 29)
  - 50th anniversary edition press materials, 1957-2009 (Box 267, Folder 30)
  - The Elements of Style by William Strunk Jr., Undated (Box 267, Folder 31)
    Copy of the original booklet printed in Ithaca, NY.
  - Correspondence with J.G. Cage (of Macmillan Co.), 1959-1962 (Box 267, Folder 32)
    Letter to his alma mater Williams College and from Katherine White - grammar related.
- Book on E.B. White by Others
  - Scott Elledge, E.B. White: A Biography
    - Galley proofs
      - 1 (Box 244)
      - 2 (Box 245)
      - 3 (Box 246)
      - 4 (Box 247)
    - First draft and photographs and negatives (Box 248)
    - Second draft, Chapters I-VII (Box 249)
    - Second draft, Chapters VII-X (Box 250)
    - First complete text, Chapters I-IV (Box 250)
    - First complete text, Chapters V-X (Box 251)
    - Second text ( 1980 ), Chapters I-X (Box 252)
    - Second text ( 1980 ), Chapters XI-XV (Box 253)
    - Typescript, Chapters XI-XVIII (annotated) (Box 253)
    - Copy-edited typescript (Box 254)
    - Note Cards (Box 259)
    - Poster for the book (Folder 2)
  - Katherine Romans Hall, E.B. White: A Bibliographic Catalogue
    - Original manuscript (Box 255)
    - Publisher's copy I (Box 256)
    - Publisher's copy II (Box 257)
- Miscellaneous (mainly oversize)
  - Record Labels, Undated (Box 260, Folder 9)
    Loose labels from recordings of James Thurber's The 13 Clocks; Stuart Little; and Charlotte's Web
  - Musical scores by S.T. White, c. 1875 (Box 260, Folder 5-6)
    "Sweet Dreams of Childhood" and "Debut Waltz"
  - Musical scores by unknown composer, Undated (Box 260, Folder 7)
    "We Parted in Sadness"
  - E.B. White's desk (with pencil sharpener), MU-2124
  - E.B. White's typewriter, MU-2125
  - E.B. White's table, MU-2126
  - Stuart Little roadster, Undated; MU-2288 (Box 262)
- Adaptations, Films, and Recordings
  - Adaptations and Recordings of Charlotte's Web
    - E.B. White reads Charlotte's Web, Undated; SR-6345-6348 (Box 260)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapters 1 and 2, Undated; Cassette TR-10536 and 10546 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapter 3, Undated; Cassette TR-10537-10539 (Box 264)
      3 copies
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapter 4, Undated; Cassette TR-10540-10541 (Box 264)
      2 copies
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapter 5, Undated; Cassette TR-10542-10543 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapter 6, Undated; Cassette TR-10544-10545 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapters 7 and 8, Undated; Cassette TR-10547-10548 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapter 9, Undated; Cassette TR-10549 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapter 10, Undated; Cassette TR-10550 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapters 11 and 12, Undated; Cassette TR-10551 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapter 13, Undated; Cassette TR-10552 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapters 14 and 15, Undated; Cassette TR-10553 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapter 16, Undated; Cassette TR-10554 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapter 17, Undated; Cassette TR-10555 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapter 18, Undated; Cassette TR-10556 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapter 20, Undated; Cassette TR-10557 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapter 21, Undated; Cassette TR-10558 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web - Chapter 22, Undated; Cassette TR-10559 (Box 264)
    - E.B. White Reads Charlotte's Web: Film Strips - Chapters 1-22, Undated (Box 264)
      For use in a classroom
      19 canisters - missing Chapter 9
    - Original pencil sketches and cels from the animated film Charlotte's Web, 1973 (Box 266, Folder 3)
      Hannah-Barbera Production
    - Original color sketch from the animated film Charlotte's Web, 1973 (Folder 1)
  - Adaptations and Recordings of Stuart Little
    - Julie Harris reads Stuart Little, Undated; SR-6343-6344 (Box 260)
      Part 1 and 2
    - Stuart Little - Music, Undated; Cassette TR-10560 (Box 264)
      "Growing Up" and "Jolly Thomas"
    - Still photographs from TV adaptation of Stuart Little, 1965 (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Storyboards for Stuart Little Chapters 8-15, Undated (Folder 1)
  - Films and Recordings (not based on books)
    - Meet the Newberry Author: E.B. White, 1985; Cassette TR-10563 (Box 260)
      Tape recording, film strip, and media gram
      Does not contain E.B. White's voice
    - Layout of E.B. White filmstrip by Random House, Undated (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - "The Right of Privacy", July, 1977; 5in Reel TR-10528 (Box 264)
      WLBZ radio interview.
      Use TR-10531
    - "The Right of Privacy", July, 1977; Cassette TR-10531 (Box 264)
      Copy of TR-10528
    - "The Xerox Matter", July, 1976; 7in Reel TR-10530 (Box 264)
      Radio Station WDEA interview.
      Use TR-10533
    - "The Xerox Matter", July, 1976; Cassette TR-10533 (Box 264)
      Copy of TR-10530
    - "E.B. White Recalls Cornell Years", October, 1964; 7in Reel TR-10529 (Box 264)
      Interview by Susan Frank for the Cornell Daily Sun.
      Use CD-2363
    - "E.B. White Recalls Cornell Years", October, 1964; Cassette TR-10532 (Box 264)
      Copy of TR-10529, use CD-2363.
    - "E.B. White Recalls Cornell Years", October, 1964; CD-2363 (Box 264)
      Copy of TR-10532
      Also a copy of the article from the Daily Sun, October 9, 1964, page S2, that includes a transcript.
    - Mrs. Bushong's 3rd Year Students Discussion of E.B. White s Children's Books, Undated; Cassette TR-10534 (Box 264)
      Seven Hills School, 2401 McConnell Avenue, Owensboro, Kentucky, 42301
    - Mrs. Flemmings Class, Undated; Cassette TR-10535 (Box 264)
    - The Family that Dwelt Apart, 1973; 16mm F-1086 (Box 265)
      Film with sound.
    - Maine Lobsterman, Undated; 16mm F-1087-1088 (Box 265)
      Film without sound
    - Maine Lobsterman and The Family that Dwelt Apart, Undated; U-Matic V-715
    - Camp Otter: Reels 1-3, Undated; 16mm F-1083-1085 (Box 265)
    - Little Boys in the Bush, Undated; 16mm F-1089 (Box 265)
      Fragment of film